# Jayson Wong

General Santos, Soccsksargen, Philippines

jaysonwongf@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/mrjaysonwong

# **Summary**

I am a highly self-motivated and hardworking individual, who is passionate about learning new technology stacks. My eventual career goal is to become a fully qualified & experienced front-end web developer.

• Working knowledge and experience in NodeJS, React, NoSQL, and some Javascript-related technologies.

# **Experience**

## **Front-End Web Developer**

Self-employed

Mar 2022 - Present (9 months +)

# **▶:ii** Data Production Manager

**DemandScience** 

May 2019 - May 2020 (1 year 1 month)

# **Senior Quality Assurance Specialist**

**DemandScience** 

Jun 2017 - May 2019 (2 years)

#### **Mail** Senior Q.A Lead

**DemandScience** 

Dec 2015 - May 2017 (1 year 6 months)

## Marketing Quality Analyst

Callbox USA

Jan 2015 - Nov 2015 (11 months)

#### Marketing Team Lead

Callbox USA

Jun 2014 - Dec 2014 (7 months)

#### Marketing Associate

Callbox USA

May 2013 - Jun 2014 (1 year 2 months)

#### **Education**

## **STI College of General Santos City**

Bachelor's Degree, Bachelor of Science in Information Technology 2009 - 2013

## **Licenses & Certifications**

- (A) JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures freeCodeCamp
- JavaScript Course 2021 Udemy
- The Web Developer Bootcamp 2022 Udemy
- (A) Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp
- MongoDB Basics MongoDB

### **Skills**

Website Development • CSS • JavaScript • Data Analysis • NoSQL • HTML • React.js • Next.js • Figma (Software) • Node.js